

# VINITH GOUD

CREATIVE DESIGNER

## CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 7893361112

**EMAIL:** 

vinithg666@gmail.com

**ADDRESS:** 

Hyderabad

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a passionate Creative Designer having expertise of 4 years. I work closely with my clients in developing strong brand identities that define and exhibit values, and also professional visual entities to define your tone. I am a strong team player and a social butterfly.

#### **SKILLS**

Adobe Creative Cloud

Video Editing

**UI** Design

Graphic Design

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Graphic designer

Preeminent Technology | 2021 - Present

Working as a Graphic Designer for 3-4 clints, Creating Brands, websits and managing digital marketing campaigns over social media

- Upgrated the communication Skills
- · Team leading skills

# Photographer / Designer

MIVI - CASEON | 2019 - 2021

Worked as a Product Photographer and Designer, Made some eye catchee images and designs for website.

- · Upgrated the Editing Skills
- Image manpulation and color matching

### **EDUCATION**

#### Bachelors Of Fine Arts

Osmania University | 2016 - 2019

I finished my bachelor's college in between busy working and I graduated on time with the best grades.

- Upgraded the skill in Software's
- Design problem solving